soyouwanna.com 2006-12-05

# SoYouWanna.com

**Effective as of June 3, 2005**

**THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK THIS PAGE FOR UPDATES OR REQUEST THE LATEST COPY BY[ **CONTACTING US ONLINE**](http://www.intermix.com/form_privacy.cfm?site=soyouwanna.com).**

Intermix Network, LLC owns and/or operates a network of Web sites (referred to hereafter as the "Network") providing diversionary entertainment and topical news, information and editorial content to millions of users and subscribers daily. The information collection, use, maintenance and disposal practices of the Network are discussed in this privacy policy.

**1\. Collection of Information.**

**1.1 Survey Information.**  
The Network collects information from individuals when such individuals voluntarily complete Network surveys, order forms, send an email through the Network's referral engine technology or submit information via an online forms which may or may not be accompanied by a pre-checked or non-pre-checked checkbox indicating that such individuals consent to receiving marketing communications from the Network (a "Co-registration"), or a registration pages either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (each, a "Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the websites and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, via postal mail, telephones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, the Network or a third party may ask individuals to provide various information to the Network, which may include their name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education level, marital status, occupation, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (collectively, "Survey Information"). Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to the Network or any third party, but individuals may receive incentives from the Network or a third party in exchange for providing Survey Information to the Network.

**1.2 Other Information.**  
Other occasions when the Network obtains information from individuals include when such individuals (1) make a claim for a prize or seek to redeem an incentive offered by the Network or a third party, (2) request assistance through the Network's customer service department, and (3) voluntarily subscribe to a Network service or newsletter (collectively, "Other Information").

**1.3 Cookies, Web beacons, and Other Information Collected Using Technology.**  
The Network may use cookie technology to associate certain Internet-related information about individuals with information about such individuals in our database. Additionally, the Network may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information").

**(a) Cookies.** A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows Network to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in Network's database. You may read more about cookies at [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

**(b) Third Party Cookies.** We send to your web browser many of the advertisements you see when you use our network of Web sites. However, we also allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our web pages. Because your web browser must request these advertising banners from the ad network Web site, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file, just as if you had requested a web page from the site. Please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 13-24 who have viewed sports content) and you respond to that ad, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. As always remember, we only authorize our third-party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. Our third-party ad servers do not collect, nor do we give them access, to any personally identifying information about you.

**Opting Out of Third-Party Ad Servers** If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network's Web site individually and opt out (if they offer this capability). Currently, we have relationships with the following third-party ad networks (click to visit their Web site): 24/7 Real Media, Inc. <http://www.247realmedia.com/privacy.html>

**(c) Web beacons.** Web beacons are graphic images, often transparent and no larger than 1 pixel x 1 pixel, that are placed on a Web site or in an e-mail. Web beacons are used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the Web site or opening the e-mail. When the HTML code for the Web beacon points to a site to retrieve the image, it simultaneously can pass along information such as the IP address of the computer that retrieved the image, the time the Web beacon was viewed and for how long, the type of browser that retrieved the image and previously set cookie values. The Network, or third parties acting on the Network's behalf, may utilize Web beacons on Web pages or in email for any legally permissible purpose.

**(d) General Behavior Tracking.** The Network may track online behaviors ("Behaviors") through its own technologies, including its desktop software products, in order to increase the effectiveness of the advertisements it delivers. Examples of such behaviors may include advertisement responses, websites that individuals visit, and products that individuals purchase. Individuals can prevent the tracking of Behaviors by globally unsubscribing from the Network's marketing materials. As described in Section 2.1, the Network reserves the right to use such technologies for any purpose permitted by law.

**(e) Information Automatically Collected.** For site maintenance, optimization, security and other legally permissible purposes, the Network's servers (or third party servers) may collect certain information about website visitors automatically. Such information may include such visitors' IP address, browser type, date, time and duration of visit and particular pages viewed, and such other information as is permitted by law.

**(f) New Technology.** The use of technology on the Internet is rapidly evolving, as is the Network's use of new technology. As previously stated, Network reserves the right to change this policy at any time without any additional notice to the user. As a result, the Network strongly encourages individuals to revisit this privacy policy from time to time for any updates regarding its use of technology. Use of any Network website constitutes acknowledgement and acceptance of the Network's Privacy Policy and the Network's right to modify such Privacy Policy without additional notice.

**1.4 Outside Information.** The Network may receive information about individuals from a third party or from other sources of information outside of the Network including information located in public databases ("Outside Information").

**1.5 Individual Information.** As used herein, "Individual Information" means Survey Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information the Network gathers or receives about individuals.

**1.6 No Information Collected from Children.** The Network will never knowingly or intentionally collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If the Network obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not knowingly or intentionally collect such information, to the best of the Network's knowledge and belief, the Network has no such information to use or to disclose to a third party. The Network has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

**1.7 Credit Card Information.** The Network may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from Network. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to the Network, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. The Network will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

**2\. Use of Individual Information.**

**2.1 Discretion to Use Information.**  
THE NETWORK MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN THE NETWORK'S SOLE DISCRETION. The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how the Network currently uses Individual Information, but the Network may change or broaden its use at any time as permitted by law. As noted below, the Network may update this policy from time to time. The Network may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, and online banner advertising, among other uses. 

**2.2 Email.**  
The Network uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals who have permitted use of their email address for this purpose. The Network may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe. 

**2.3 Targeted Advertising.**  
The Network uses Individual Information to target advertising to individuals. When individuals use the Internet, the Network uses such persons' Individual Information to show advertising for products and services in which those users have expressed an interest, whether directly or indirectly. 

**2.4 Direct Mail and Telemarketing.**  
The Network may use Individual Information to advertise or provide promotional offers, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones, as permitted by law. 

**2.6 Storage of Individual Information.**  
The Network stores Individual Information in a database on Network computers. Network computers have security measures (such as firewalls) in place to reasonably protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under the Network's control. Notwithstanding such measures, the Network cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Network computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered. 

**2.7 Rights of Third Party Affiliates.**  
Network may extend any of its rights under this Agreement to third parties performing services on its behalf. 

**3\. Dissemination of Individual Information.**

**3.1 Sale to Third Parties.**  
The Network may sell or transfer Individual Information to third parties in connection with any merger, acquisition, reorganization, change in capital structure, sale of all or substantially all of the assets of any Network division or website, or any activity specified in Section 3.2, 3.3, or 3.4 below. 

**3.2 Order Fulfillment.**  
The Network will transfer Individual Information to third parties as necessary to provide a product or service that an individual orders from such third party while using one of the Network's websites or when responding to offers provided by the Network. 

**3.3 Legal Process.**  
The Network may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, or other legal process. 

**3.4 Summary Data.**  
The Network may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons. 

**4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.**

**4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons.**  
Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (collectively, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Network's websites and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. The Network does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and the Network has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. 

**4.2 Links.**  
The Network's websites and email messages may contain hypertext links to the websites of one or more third parties. The Network is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. 

**4.3 Affiliated Companies.**  
The Network may disclose, transfer and sell Individual Information to an entity which becomes affiliated with Network through formation, merger or acquisition, in the Network's discretion. 

**5\. Unsubscribe from Intermix lists.**  
The Network maintains multiple newsletter and email marketing lists. To unsubscribe from one or more of such lists, click the link included in the footer of any message delivered by the Network and follow the instructions provided. 

**6\. More Information.**  
For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit [www.privacylaw.net](http://www.privacylaw.net/) or [www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/). If you have questions about this policy, please [contact us online](http://www.intermix.com/form_privacy.cfm?site=soyouwanna.com). THE NETWORK RESERVES THE RIGHT TO UPDATE THIS POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME, SO YOU SHOULD REVIEW THIS WEB PAGE PERIODICALLY.
